<resources>
    <string name="app_name">GenshinApp</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <!-- Strings used for fragments for navigation -->
    <string name="first_fragment_label">First Fragment</string>
    <string name="second_fragment_label">Second Fragment</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="previous">Previous</string>

    <string name="hello_first_fragment">Hello first fragment</string>
    <string name="hello_second_fragment">Hello second fragment. Arg: %1$s</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="overview"><b>Overview</b></string>
    <string name="jeanOverview_txt">

        <p><b>Jean Gunnhildr</b> is a playable <b>Anemo</b> character in
        <i>Genshin Impact</i>. She is the daughter of <b>Frederica Gunnhildr</b> and <b>Seamus Pegg</b>,
        and the older sister of <b>Barbara</b>.</p>

        <!-- Jean Text -->

    </string>
    <string name="jeanOverview2_txt">

        <p> A descendant of the prestigious <b>Gunnhildr Clan</b>, Jean is the Acting Grand Master of the
        <b>Knights of Favoius</b>. She is always busy handling unrest across <b>Mondstadt</b> and
            of course, tirelessly working to maintain the City of Freedom. </p>

    </string>

    <!-- Lisa Text -->

    <string name="lisaOverview_txt">
        <p><b>Lisa Minci</b> is a playable <b>Electro</b> character in <i>Genshin Impact.</i> She
            is received for free in the Prologue <b>Act I: The Outlander Who Caught the Wind</b>
            during the quest <b>Sparks Amongst the Pages.</b></p>
    </string>

    <string name="lisaOverview2_txt">
        <p>Once a grand mage recognized as the <b>Sumeru Academia</b>\'s most distinguished graduate
        in 200 years, Lisa has since returned to Mondstadt to become the humble Librarian of the
        <b>Knights of Favonius</b>.</p>
    </string>

    <!-- Eula Text -->

    <string name="eulaOverview_txt">
        <p><b>Eula Lawrence</b> is a playable <b>Cryo</b> character in <i>Genshin Impact</i>.</p>
    </string>

    <string name="eulaOverview2_txt">
        <p>A descendant of the infamous and tyrannical <b>Lawrence Clan</b> and niece of
            <b>Schubert</b>, Eula is the captain of the Reconnaissance Company with the
            <b>Knights of Favonius</b>.
        </p>
    </string>

    <!-- Venti Text -->

    <string name="ventiOverview_txt">
    <p><b>Venti</b> is a free-spirited, wine-loving bard in <b>Mondstadt</b> and the current
    mortal vessel of <b>Barbatos</b>, the <b>Anemo Archon</b>. He is also a playable
    <b>Anemo</b> character in <i>Genshin Impact</i>.</p>
    </string>

    <string name="ventiOverview2_txt">
    <p>He first appears during the <b>Archon Quest Prologue</b>: Act I - <b>The Outlander Who
    Caught the Wind</b>.
    </p>
    </string>

    <!-- Diluc Text -->

    <string name="dilucOverview_txt">
    <p><b>Diluc Ragnvindr</b> is a playable <b>Pyro</b> character in <i>Genshin Impact</i>.</p>
    </string>

    <string name="dilucOverview2_txt">
    <p>Born  into the affluent <b>Ragnvindr Clan</b>, Diluc is the current owner of the <b>Dawn
    Winery</b> and a nobleman of high esteem in <b>Mondstadt</b> society. While a past incident
        caused him to split ways with the <b>Knights of Favonius</b>, he continues to protect
        Mondstadt in his own way.
    </p>
    </string>

    <!-- Klee Text -->

    <string name="kleeOverview_txt">
    <p><b>Klee</b> is a playable <b>Pyro</b> character in <i>Genshin Impact</i>.</p>
    </string>

    <string name="kleeOverview2_txt">
    <p>The daughter of the intrepid - and destructive - adventurer <b>Alice</b>, Klee takes after
        her mother in many ways, much to the consternation of the <b>Knights of Favonius</b> whom
        she has been entrusted to.
    </p>
    </string>

    <!-- Mona Text -->

    <string name="monaOverview_txt">
    <p><b>Mona Megistus</b> is a playable <b>Hydro</b> character in <i>Genshin Impact</i>.</p>
    </string>

    <string name="monaOverview2_txt">
    <p>An astrologist of great skill and equally-great pride, Mona has taken up residence in <b>
        Mondstadt</b> to avoid incurring the wrath of her master after unwittingly reading the
        latter\'s diary.
    </p>
    </string>

    <!-- Albedo Text -->

    <string name="albedoOverview_txt">
    <p><b>Albedo</b>, also known as the <b>Kreideprinz</b>, is a playable <b>Geo</b> character in
    <i>Genshin Impact</i>.</p>
    </string>

    <string name="albedoOverview2_txt">
    <p>The mysterious Albedo is the Chief Alchemist and Captain of the Investigation Team of the
        <b>Knights of Favonius</b> through a recommendation from the adventurer <b>Alice</b>, with
        <b>Sucrose</b> as his assistant. He holds an infinite desire to learn about the world of
        Teyvat, carefully studying every object around him.
    </p>
    </string>

    <!-- Amber Text -->

    <string name="amberOverview_txt">
    <p><b>Amber</b> is a playable <b>Pyro</b> character in <i>Genshin Impact</i>. She is
    received for free in the Prologue <b>Act I: The Outlander Who Caught the Wind</b> during
    the quest <b>Winds of the Past</b>.</p>
    </string>

    <string name="amberOverview2_txt">
    <p>Amber is the only remaining Outrider of the <b>Knights of Favonius</b>. She is always ready
        to help the citizens of <b>Mondstadt</b> - whether it be something ismple or perhaps a more
        challenging task.
    </p>
    </string>

    <!-- Kaeya Text -->

    <string name="kaeyaOverview_txt">
    <p><b>Kaeya Alberich</b> is a playable <b>Cryo</b> character in <i>Genshin Impact</i>. He is
    received for free in the Prologue, Act I: <b>The Outlander Who Caught the Wind</b> during
    the quest <b>Crash Course</b>.</p>
    </string>

    <string name="kaeyaOverview2_txt">
    <p>Kaeya is a Cavalry Captain in the <b>Knights of Favonius</b>. He is held in high regard by
        the people of <b>Mondstadt</b> - even with all his eccentricities and secrets.
    </p>
    </string>

    <!-- Barbara Text -->

    <string name="barbaraOverview_txt">
    <p><b>Barbara Pegg</b> is a playable <b>Hydro</b> character in <i>Genshin Impact</i>. She is
    received for free in the <b>Baptism of Song</b> Event for completing the quest <b>A Long
        Shot</b> during the <b>Prologue</b> Act III: <b>Song of Dragon and Freedom</b>. She is
    the daughter of <b>Frederica Gunnhildr</b> and <b>Seamus Pegg</b>, and the younger sister of
    <b>Jean</b>.</p>
    </string>

    <string name="barbaraOverview2_txt">
    <p>Barbara is the deaconess of the <b>Church of Favonius</b> and a self-proclaimed "idol" after
        learning about them from the intrepid adventurer <b>Alice</b>.
    </p>
    </string>

    <!-- Razor Text -->

    <string name="razorOverview_txt">
    <p><b>Razor</b> is a playable <b>Electro</b> character in <i>Genshin Impact</i>.</p>
    </string>

    <string name="razorOverview2_txt">
        <p>Abandoned as an infant, Razor was taken in by the <b>Wolf of the North</b>, <b>Andrius</b>
            , and raised by his wolf pack in <b>Wolvendom</b>. After a chance encounter with
            <b>Varka</b>, the current Grand Master of the <b>Knights of Favonius</b> and the
            Knight of Boreas, he has slowly started integrating with humans again.
        </p>
    </string>

    <!-- Bennett Text -->

    <string name="bennettOverview_txt">
    <p><b>Bennett</b> is a playable <b>Pyro</b> character in <i>Genshin Impact</i>.</p>
    </string>

    <string name="bennettOverview2_txt">
        <p>An orphan discovered by an elderly adventurer as a baby, Bennett was raised in
            <b>Mondstadt</b>\'s <b>Adventurers\' Guild</b>. He is the only member of "<b>Benny\'s
            Adventure Team</b>," as everyone else left the team after experiencing the constant
            misfortune that follows him.
        </p>
    </string>

    <!-- Noelle Text -->

    <string name="noelleOverview_txt">
    <p><b>Noelle</b> is a playable <b>Geo</b> character in <i>Genshin Impact</i>.</p>
    </string>

    <string name="noelleOverview2_txt">
        <p>While not yet a knight, she seeks to one day join the <b>Knights of Favonius</b> by
            first serving as a dutiful maid.
        </p>
    </string>

    <!-- Fischl Text -->

    <string name="fischlOverview_txt">
    <p><b>Fischl</b> is a playable <b>Electro</b> character in <i>Genshin Impact</i>.</p>
    </string>

    <string name="fischlOverview2_txt">
        <p>Fischl is an investigator for <b>Mondstadt</b>\'s <b>Adventurer\'s Guild</b>,
            accompanied by the night raven <b>Oz</b>. Fischl claims to hail from a world beyond
            <b>Teyvat</b>. She is a daring adventurer with seemly outlandish theories that happen
            to turn out to be true.
        </p>
    </string>

    <!-- Sucrose Text -->

    <string name="sucroseOverview_txt">
    <p><b>Sucrose</b> is a playable <b>Anemo</b> character in <i>Genshin Impact</i>.</p>
    </string>

    <string name="sucroseOverview2_txt">
        <p>An alchemist specializing in bio-alchemy, she also serves as an assistant for
            <b>Albedo</b>, the head alchemist of the <b>Knights of Favonius</b>.
        </p>
    </string>

    <!-- Diona Text -->

    <string name="dionaOverview_txt">
    <p><b>Diona</b> is a playable <b>Cryo</b> character in <i>Genshin Impact</i>. She is the
        daughter of <b>Draff</b>, a hunter in Springvale.</p>
    </string>

    <string name="dionaOverview2_txt">
        <p>Despite being a bartender at <b>Cat\'s Tail</b>, she actually despises alcohol and wants
        nothing more than to ruin <b>Mondstadt</b>\'s wine industry - a feat easier said than
        done when her patrons absolutely love her drinks.
        </p>
    </string>

</resources>